[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "How long can they continue to interrogate him for?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "can", "they", "continue", "to", "interrogate", "him", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, they can interview him as many times as he is willing to do so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "can", "interview", "him", "as", "many", "times", "as", "he", "is", "willing", "to", "do", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "PERSON": ["Zubeidat Tsarnaev"]}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "They say how could these good Muslims do this, kill innocent people, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["They", "say", "how", "could", "these", "good", "Muslims", "do", "this", ",", "kill", "innocent", "people", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Right, and this denial is led by their mother, Zubeidat Tsarnaev, who gave this extraordinary interview to CNN.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "and", "this", "denial", "is", "led", "by", "their", "mother", ",", "Zubeidat", "Tsarnaev", ",", "who", "gave", "this", "extraordinary", "interview", "to", "CNN", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "And the younger one?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "younger", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "The youngest one, I would say probably two years for the first two years.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "youngest", "one", ",", "I", "would", "say", "probably", "two", "years", "for", "the", "first", "two", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Did he explain why he needed it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "explain", "why", "he", "needed", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"]}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "He would you describe his behavior?", "question_tokens": ["He", "would", "you", "describe", "his", "behavior", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "On Tuesday was the first time that I see him acting the way he was acting.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "Tuesday", "was", "the", "first", "time", "that", "I", "see", "him", "acting", "the", "way", "he", "was", "acting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Did he pay you for the repair works to the car?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "pay", "you", "for", "the", "repair", "works", "to", "the", "car", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "How would you describe him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "He's always quiet.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "always", "quiet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "How would you describe him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Very kind.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "kind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Did anything in his behavioral pattern in the last few months say to you something is not quite right here?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "anything", "in", "his", "behavioral", "pattern", "in", "the", "last", "few", "months", "say", "to", "you", "something", "is", "not", "quite", "right", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I saw him two weeks before the incident and he was exactly the same Dzhokhar as always.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "him", "two", "weeks", "before", "the", "incident", "and", "he", "was", "exactly", "the", "same", "Dzhokhar", "as", "always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Can you believe that he is capable of doing what he has alleged to have done?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "believe", "that", "he", "is", "capable", "of", "doing", "what", "he", "has", "alleged", "to", "have", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I mean, it's really hard to think about it just because you never think that one of your friends can just become a terrorist any time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "hard", "to", "think", "about", "it", "just", "because", "you", "never", "think", "that", "one", "of", "your", "friends", "can", "just", "become", "a", "terrorist", "any", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "A political nature?", "question_tokens": ["A", "political", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I know he followed Islamic stuff on Twitter.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "he", "followed", "Islamic", "stuff", "on", "Twitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What did he say about his demeanor?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "about", "his", "demeanor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Two of my friends saw him at the gym the day after the bombing at like 9:00 or 10:00 at night, they said.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "of", "my", "friends", "saw", "him", "at", "the", "gym", "the", "day", "after", "the", "bombing", "at", "like", "9:00", "or", "10:00", "at", "night", ",", "they", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Not true?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Not true.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "ENNEBERRY: No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["ENNEBERRY", ":", "No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "A lot of blood?", "question_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "blood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "A good amount of blood.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "good", "amount", "of", "blood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What were you thinking at that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "thinking", "at", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Oh my God.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "I mean, you couldn't make that up, could you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "could", "n't", "make", "that", "up", ",", "could", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "You can't!", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "What was the moment like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "It was probably one of the most amazing spiritual moments of my life, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "probably", "one", "of", "the", "most", "amazing", "spiritual", "moments", "of", "my", "life", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "You walked in to see her at the hospital and what happened?", "question_tokens": ["You", "walked", "in", "to", "see", "her", "at", "the", "hospital", "and", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "We met.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "met", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Did she thank you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "thank", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "OBB: She seems to be doing really well.", "answer_tokens": ["OBB", ":", "She", "seems", "to", "be", "doing", "really", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "(on the phone): I'm overwhelmed.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "on", "the", "phone", ")", ":", "I", "'m", "overwhelmed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "What were you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "You just said it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "just", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Do you have a suspicion as to who has done this to you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "suspicion", "as", "to", "who", "has", "done", "this", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I do now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "The person you believe did this to you, why would they do that to you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "person", "you", "believe", "did", "this", "to", "you", ",", "why", "would", "they", "do", "that", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Well, you know, I am an entertainer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "am", "an", "entertainer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "But Kevin, this particular guy that you -- I think it's a man that you suspect, have you had an ongoing feud with him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "Kevin", ",", "this", "particular", "guy", "that", "you", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "man", "that", "you", "suspect", ",", "have", "you", "had", "an", "ongoing", "feud", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kevin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Have you met this person?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "this", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Was it a hostile encounter?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "a", "hostile", "encounter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Have they led you to believe that will happen?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "led", "you", "to", "believe", "that", "will", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "To my understanding, he already is and his home is quarantined by the federal agent.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "my", "understanding", ",", "he", "already", "is", "and", "his", "home", "is", "quarantined", "by", "the", "federal", "agent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Are you performing?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "performing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I'm going to be on \"Good Morning America\" in the morning.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "be", "on", "``", "Good", "Morning", "America", "''", "in", "the", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "But if she is, the FBI, who she is talking about there, is being in repeated contract with both Tamerlan Tsarnaev and with her, have questions to answer, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "she", "is", ",", "the", "FBI", ",", "who", "she", "is", "talking", "about", "there", ",", "is", "being", "in", "repeated", "contract", "with", "both", "Tamerlan", "Tsarnaev", "and", "with", "her", ",", "have", "questions", "to", "answer", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "PERSON": ["Tamerlan Tsarnaev"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "What could they have done legally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "they", "have", "done", "legally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Well, civil libertarians are very concerned about surveiling every suspicious person.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "civil", "libertarians", "are", "very", "concerned", "about", "surveiling", "every", "suspicious", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "To me, this all stinks to high heaven of some other entity being involved, because they couldn't have just learned all this stuff, could they, from the Internet?", "question_tokens": ["To", "me", ",", "this", "all", "stinks", "to", "high", "heaven", "of", "some", "other", "entity", "being", "involved", ",", "because", "they", "could", "n't", "have", "just", "learned", "all", "this", "stuff", ",", "could", "they", ",", "from", "the", "Internet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "But the bottom line is this: do you believe there is any link between Tamerlan Tsarnaev and this triple killing involving one of his best friends?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "bottom", "line", "is", "this", ":", "do", "you", "believe", "there", "is", "any", "link", "between", "Tamerlan", "Tsarnaev", "and", "this", "triple", "killing", "involving", "one", "of", "his", "best", "friends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Well, I believe that there's enough information that has come to light since the bombings that will cause investigators to take another really close, hard look at this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "there", "'s", "enough", "information", "that", "has", "come", "to", "light", "since", "the", "bombings", "that", "will", "cause", "investigators", "to", "take", "another", "really", "close", ",", "hard", "look", "at", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "And what was the belief at the time in terms of who had done it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "belief", "at", "the", "time", "in", "terms", "of", "who", "had", "done", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Well, I think the belief at the time was that this was probably a drug-related murder.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "belief", "at", "the", "time", "was", "that", "this", "was", "probably", "a", "drug-related", "murder", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130423pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "What are your memories of that day, given the appalling events that happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "memories", "of", "that", "day", ",", "given", "the", "appalling", "events", "that", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Well, I was stopped about eight blocks from the finish line.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "stopped", "about", "eight", "blocks", "from", "the", "finish", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]